[
    {
        "question": "cCAjUw+ogWOKCo/HDDL4kF3BMX37v3DBgXbLiLuCDVdjRsPolDu+yyDNAgeXcXbLVqS1JqXuSsDu1PWIbvZ4FCn8iZXiPC4a2EJZJdYjqiKMaTz0zdUylJnQ7hdvlqXnkVY1Y8hGvlzbgHFrcaewJH5/PRTc65IFQGllmhG40bY+2Jr2KWdqZp8e0E6XVEz/WX24fUpK+oOrfHlGkn1P2jPtO8oDRA+gFaCLzO92Sv/Bhzyyan1gwgI7GkWE6dxrTJzsu8CZvqWb8aRK4whfv3R4Recphrxag+bTHI2atJlIrS4VTDMrc3A6Swf8SzTTgF8sF032GhOXu/9QXbKC4eNqln5NuJlgKTGxLIyTRM5Lr5fShcSwSoYUutGPpOXrlgQd3qKZ/Zf6KqWrTS+4vJqCKlgs6kGD3WSSX0s88ySML6fGpWhBCSvCwy1OfdwYaK6h/HAtvJix7KeJ62MZ1OxVnwt9oY1e/h34qHzuzWg1S1RMUBI+gz7VAUSdb+24zxVrfOy9qzQxhlh6Xm7GFF6LVmuseWQQTx0yGYVeppO7zsXnQBqWwjcQBMl78h3FLboklBAQPbgRivwMqk+MdBY9+c4OlIa0tpvejMWosHFAsPhz/SI9nyNRWAudi1Ox",
        "questionId": "9b8dec7cddbd4dcea38ec92ce42b0bee",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "iTCrxx4zbK9epP6eImLSB4P2XAMwr21vc1HtRIBYk7E=",
                "optionId": "e48c85689dc34af38de99b5e1bcad57d"
            },
            {
                "option": "K5gnje/OuuWi7uYTyfstyypQgQL5JKgGRzLLD9P1f5M=",
                "optionId": "0de26e055759457ab2bb20e0fdbd3e90"
            },
            {
                "option": "1WWBKnUl1npLMUGiG5kx4yoOrP35XmsGFm293ByHOJM=",
                "optionId": "7a7fab9358454bb59fb6e333b540e721"
            },
            {
                "option": "iEXpvFtCkh+st9sZ36WkAqeGtSQUxt87hslkhXUc7PVFeXOV/B5DdY2qoxvjUj2w",
                "optionId": "883c5f85320b480aa3eecba41bddc819"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "7a7fab9358454bb59fb6e333b540e721",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "NOdip/6wo+lowYqY29lOGZ150arKDLyUGvMiTbnkyFbkYZZfLKO9KSRQ0TVdOcIKsklQE00ohqYjV62CmcymXf2DxGKa6LG0O5yIUWOSGWgiwy5wjPFxcF1WzlFEhn7IThrzUnTABbAEI8/YtEw8nG+v6B/9Ai+BZPqPPs30dvz+BnLLub358vJtL8iU8WjZo6czsGPxja2qlkhqUIgZjGJSz0gsaqHSX2fM8VGS4fx9JmKQt5aZC3+KHP5i/LQ7sihWwYR1cyqjzFawPiBfFy27AK5735Q03x4Ez+EzUa7ITLYjbQ8sOR6VRP8LeTWs",
        "questionId": "1e4357f320d74712a0a93d16fb5c8a57",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "HuRGylEaWdvup0ylZzLcCMOST5z27RuZyTTFhLikmwo=",
                "optionId": "374b4ddfb6aa41f78cbc64e514c27cde"
            },
            {
                "option": "qtRiLJWYDoJ8Ys203cI7KfOoPbpEGPX+r4l6HJrLQEo=",
                "optionId": "b84d6bbdccd140368df911a2f09ccf47"
            },
            {
                "option": "gmSnMdt3JwDyGYkNozyuMQYJPzgn0vJ3bs9P1cjaksM=",
                "optionId": "054dfae693b240cbb687c598f7675b2d"
            },
            {
                "option": "FDPrrnjUZJTkmz7N/K0/+sRrAjON0iJmMBJy3biMJpo=",
                "optionId": "cca766aa5933489ab9f3aca21e61c933"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "cca766aa5933489ab9f3aca21e61c933",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "86KxmKLALI8p+dwj6T7zng/OSfEWUaFqT8m5HWEzkIeQTpG/G0TWuDMbd2UXBheRa1MEw5omkFjEllEO+i1EoHl3clm9pmFB8naCVogYvIjnGOwhhc//GojACynPOqnk+a1Iortlucu3HHZY30C9HerhiHfAyOFZ87mu3foZJJySUb949C//Tj434bQt9r8Xt5qv2iFfxqkDBS2imKDY3c2aSMSepPToEWtwlEDhgISeY3yQNSn04/rZ+q68zEiMYn8D8N3XhHBWWAoIzvUK99IE8hOfI8f2n40+dqXDDeAiMkSfuTC13Svp8IL30v/e53gpj5b1LUo7kI4bfy74xpg4u/wifyV3vk/G2IWO42lZQ4Lqaavk+2NZTh34FTxqmUx9r38/3VTFlWXs1+nB6rcdUiIyfO2hOZZ9mAqw5W0=",
        "questionId": "c88c3716f5d447038ca34bbd37adbd0b",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "Ntihw5ffgl6fahZslzFezafT5Vd0o73qiaLsQJmk02g=",
                "optionId": "3b493bd9e89f460c9a5a7d2406909164"
            },
            {
                "option": "cACo/DTgPSXphjiRXa3b5vjg8h5O3G36uhK3CcJF3UA=",
                "optionId": "96cd9c59414f423c8a6738f645021fa4"
            },
            {
                "option": "Mo8ZN8KQki54EBGxhJ5iWSnLq+7lyUBFb/tbvva2G9E=",
                "optionId": "ff97def756f74868ae79115d38c39f28"
            },
            {
                "option": "nk9v1S4Wk6NkCIhHd3qJnGGhvkb4A9XYDyP8w06nFg4=",
                "optionId": "b49ea031d284480b84cc1289ac18ac82"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "ff97def756f74868ae79115d38c39f28",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "1+90Dj8ZRAiQSNnEu9PJCwU4N+nWJWVpnjpdWWX2SVFOwgZusZ1ZE4ah/N2uIIPRW0QUC2E1aAalqBAB7ylfMZezANu1zoegz/6dYuQdo8aGnLh/L5Jhq29K1Jb/O3a3jIfCsPuBkIRJmz0PnSs5UbIlnoNizHkkdYyK9D5AGoMmV3K5lYNAxDK67ssvkyw1L211HISCVtGMloNgQoZ7oBwzYmOhKoxqEDXdRIJiuvxK/Br4p8ucLRhwv61rq+pfAzBDkNvrgb/Lf06+HJ2u8uPXK528IVUZ6X+ULc3yHMkqQF5RrpisnUZ/l0p6SWOK9LT4CvwdJKYXlLgsqPJ7di9/I7rDQVKcdz90g+GmfhsKH/4iG9OR4rLHn1hLXivulypdPAQ8FI1YL3smKPiRcgNg2ugkGCCWVQjy0rGIXnnCFDuZEivx9To2rsyXpKcMidqw/cDLMPPDEVJetRMEUw==",
        "questionId": "b38ea6ff6a4947eabc654ef01a0dc319",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "22eTT+O7qEln/PdjXs5e0DJNC4oG4RUwgLVYIZZKvBg=",
                "optionId": "51f6d59549254f4198139e4fd7c3fba3"
            },
            {
                "option": "xlZXWmS/opQPX6ycyKEb5zx71T8GXzSos+BK2kz+N4A=",
                "optionId": "149055ecdf8a43b1915b2bdd68a9f7c3"
            },
            {
                "option": "TWcSUIk7YrLH931SPrfLY4Dlrar7qUIhyZ8T9WaZ6aw=",
                "optionId": "db0cc04661c5437d8e6eec57a6dc89d4"
            },
            {
                "option": "xe4+qbLhI0xXHngZ0TQdL9r97QFy4Ra/je+GyRFFn7E=",
                "optionId": "1d161cc00e924619a13dae3ff3285954"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "149055ecdf8a43b1915b2bdd68a9f7c3",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "m+WtBxdRSwztlWHyJ3axL15vNGPbEGByroAZ7EMM6tZ8vAK2qHpuo7r9QCqlkOVnedornK4I7U8Uzcfn9e+QfhACSkwWYbEXVnWTTchLuSJbmhkFXuk7M+Y3tyMlm6mrRRzDubEuC2w+s9JvdKnzcOuq9AnOWlan1MnkgJHgjmsxJnM8uI2F2Z0qqc8TdhpM1Y6E4bN9aFl8tcbTfcXwsA==",
        "questionId": "dda9e5ab0ee744778d764f808e77574b",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "Rd7ObENU1+YYEVZMleUy0OvfxYSnW/ZR/OmF9hTnpMc=",
                "optionId": "a0187396c28b4d43877b1b9c3b8adf56"
            },
            {
                "option": "uj7kgl+zDnGKqcX0d/Wkx9263+DMbSHXOI9f/kkLXbo=",
                "optionId": "46f934136c1b43bf8f6b23a0e4dc93bb"
            },
            {
                "option": "HPvxrWnx+z/z3s6Gr+rv6ZVCaTNdA01h8N++W1VjBbI=",
                "optionId": "44bee0a78923437d89272da56d1dcb1f"
            },
            {
                "option": "Hoqq8RNNiVp69oR+q28GNr2fzns3ww8HwhQeeN78nys=",
                "optionId": "839488824c90481b896982770aafb0fe"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "46f934136c1b43bf8f6b23a0e4dc93bb",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "272GsMrq3jusoyLEo58Eoov4g1p/YIkdiYB8BufTbxsanU9zBwDz6P4MErzvFzdE0Ayc+afI2PxPwQE6jH2Jhw5RCsQjsz1Yl9HkJGWf2RjUWR1KyCZLStO6SsN3f9PZwIcfgVx9MxEhgxr1FuIoamX+8MNvXZNLd922O+B7coouib7lbOKtQ9VGqK4dDBlcXXWNHyT8jkd2WKAzW+nb3g==",
        "questionId": "3e10f6acc428468db8585dcdf397634f",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "wHHfDzEACVVOwvbwTewo1NSIiFiHAwc9YZ8w3MesdAs=",
                "optionId": "72e596c011d94410a24d5e1f5f457e18"
            },
            {
                "option": "Zw8xCU37AzavLRnHi363MMAGaljt2Chh92Znr6ys0Aw=",
                "optionId": "3a0c44ada5f24061bb3aec1d1f74daef"
            },
            {
                "option": "2SxJT7Ni9XR6c/eCAqV7bwJWC25SMtDAUjN/oM+x9J0=",
                "optionId": "a03e76f1c4cf41578ad8307d5fe23d63"
            },
            {
                "option": "Vw9AvtFVu3dsPR6i8ccg0xV21EBCkNyeH7mFv9eoEeg=",
                "optionId": "52009783a3ec44838bf0820805631537"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "3a0c44ada5f24061bb3aec1d1f74daef",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "MXkjJpaNf0QITm2r8uBH+lgwwnLbL2Vizm64XicgoPMXycQuw/eptXaSkmMHSh9qS+NrqWrDXVoSt5xwF5+1Tw==",
        "questionId": "e4e74e0a5e5a4cdd8c62efec41efe77f",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "i+/ou/o5b2l/MlNn4yjKv0w5WeXYeLDPTHI0/F0pjWI=",
                "optionId": "6638e23064d3472580752677593ef9b9"
            },
            {
                "option": "j/6+INLG3NMbpl6fnNYTLvXEAqWzT2faKcj+IBzunyc=",
                "optionId": "8699ea627f824c1a8ecf6d5809133fcb"
            },
            {
                "option": "nKeBAP6kx89mRPcIx2mGF1jFr+nD5Fb4xmjC05Q+Er4=",
                "optionId": "e6201309c2a841a49864af6ccffd55ee"
            },
            {
                "option": "dCiTu2+XXbGqE8jqk05+apvl284GjJujST4rkIJSb6w=",
                "optionId": "29d7f260d7864cbf86f719bd83076cf6"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "6638e23064d3472580752677593ef9b9",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "dOlIJhCh55PXuLPufG3gptCl2GmPxyiLQT4OIoRMviGzLb1ip55HbHbUm6BfVQ75nZ++O0/GSUI0JIGNZWYftphbIkrv6YCF8Yjq/9x7i/kANLv7yFg36vc7X7ZVxajX8c4S7QfoXmHYcHAzhGiS5oHY6bWbbEZEBqCMslLkO84TFqSO2h/0L4LemVbcm82hUTUAQ3Yf83yCS5RiCB6YH5nJOSPTk4lo48etsrYDKUOevzIoxBJB0hrC4psixTfRezLAVm+1zTQod91BJEKEF4Mz1NQtKCbaEQ1e78eiQ40N4Y0NgtHtB0pyy/EBCcQKvxPLXb65y/hoEvhXLxQV2TcQTxCQTE8U/kTAFWZQuZN7R9/9kuktoI15FcusWGXPVxAWeg9KS9jDpc8iU6eX9dEknuym4iTLp8KNFaV6ftfJgNXYujxSjGZxHm4K483QoELc8GzTmY9XNKhZpkrJCA==",
        "questionId": "b38ea6ff6a4947eabc654ef01a0dc319",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "XcEzvRKj6tqngTOYbJRhQCAZTkDrZyE8+Jwke+Wvp1s=",
                "optionId": "51f6d59549254f4198139e4fd7c3fba3"
            },
            {
                "option": "HLrr4Z/8vFv81pY5+3XNXGofPS2OzLnbDII4mYSSuY4=",
                "optionId": "149055ecdf8a43b1915b2bdd68a9f7c3"
            },
            {
                "option": "QITAzYnr95qWF0NxA2qUVuthwGfNuPwSJhufH+6z3YU=",
                "optionId": "db0cc04661c5437d8e6eec57a6dc89d4"
            },
            {
                "option": "aE32l0QIjKQHcMLO8CAnlU5yiTDoJrwRHNJbtOR+5eY=",
                "optionId": "1d161cc00e924619a13dae3ff3285954"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "149055ecdf8a43b1915b2bdd68a9f7c3",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "/lXYqomW7qsM+B3T5xePbEQ9oMVuZpZgrGgzeKlyWMx8SD0xo9qA/f6M52mRA3PCXla+PZgNb7e9cDJE0vnOMllssLkNNlxTbpuC0iHahPMQMnkVgmE7JQnQVE0PnzbOY1bFxEmog/zma80ZaovIW6a9dmMIPu0UUuc9sDYZXQM9/HC2P3CEMbyo2+ZVE9IeKFMWmsiuj7kIzo/AAy6FpBqZuZdSQXk9OxkNOv9ZF+KNqiYg9kbi9ju3OryN///J",
        "questionId": "4078bf824b7e4356a0c8002a3d3668e3",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "yfhA770cu3e5EyTAfvCFGjEma5NC9g41E76jSnlaLyg=",
                "optionId": "858179db04924481827755e02e82a7f6"
            },
            {
                "option": "LfeWBlTtGAW5jgkYWJ+re/NkwkOuVFG3tMAufgWwFjA=",
                "optionId": "144e094e4fcc4a5baf0af446a78424f6"
            },
            {
                "option": "r07aZuJ/KoUI5L5k8GwW0F0a9Ov+Si0rmWHlIeOfwY8=",
                "optionId": "6b72e027dcd44139952b28e0dd6eb995"
            },
            {
                "option": "OamldkS50iGOSGwqm89EI3UGxJp363fjkcJ5avo/nrM=",
                "optionId": "5cc599c5147047c09eaaac6d4046a691"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "6b72e027dcd44139952b28e0dd6eb995",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "EqsNX15cwJnhZXvalPV472UVbgTZW0jZKjno1sXuBHA6Yv/QFKpK0jQ0YLToX/hNREbN35LGyM9+DocY3XqgZN1wYjfu+yYK/NxZ2eLZPWuja694Oe3suBRIuOG00rHqcrzXPypG9dHM+IMhFX7EPxJeO8VJcfKixXI1TqZJk7OiJ0MfNHHiO9/yvnh44z56PNj4UM6/UZfunx22xbLnWvWupAEveZ7ZYAXic03GqUk5glKMVXr9tGZLltMbgWul6hunyvliJRQsRka6FeG/Cw==",
        "questionId": "c8a9bf5d39f844928c59dd50c1bf8cd2",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "WFWjLF4kUH3ypDOXywaU2ASqxOW67XepGILKcd5AIr0=",
                "optionId": "450a8791c19a4269958c5d05d5141118"
            },
            {
                "option": "X+uGDcEx6QyILUjCnuWgV50nWc7HZtMSQOAlacoie5c=",
                "optionId": "3ddcb96a35b14838bfec9944fca65348"
            },
            {
                "option": "FayQtgHuNCC/71OEU2oTJp7x3ASHmlwTNruHae/ilGs=",
                "optionId": "eefdce2d1eb5491a867317936514ca4e"
            },
            {
                "option": "3gxvoIoKMvTxGRoG6yNMaj2D6tbaIJSOsZOdKBj+FcA=",
                "optionId": "e1de7ff93c4540a48f92e54949c454ce"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "e1de7ff93c4540a48f92e54949c454ce",
        "center": "IIT Pallakad"
    },
    {
        "question": "i4JVRasJpcTnd/DaWpmiy2+Cdn3wS26dODR2R2mYyHbWJuWT5+lDOtfpZoIkL7qjA+rf7gXzVK3HPOx2V3b7npRM3hJ5kYgLrvRaDCZRjnPWW/1NiU2z3p53QPD/wMb/SfYEX07khzOskIZXh68QlSHeuqBkVJALLALwnlFxx9DvzU2yPwY+9yFS7DRIgAVYM/ssJW/fpmm+fYk4TSOdPUN0ytRB1ZJ0kW/DwPjDevg=",
        "questionId": "e24b5b1175cf431eac71d45a4c80c438",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "AMpmXCN9quF6auB9V3rQP1nuhldxF9ahdiVVE84L7HM=",
                "optionId": "9106cb17d795498297268ded499cf543"
            },
            {
                "option": "gL1Zxp2OXnebT/TN9J74LkwHdsQjGlLLKDjGryFr3do=",
                "optionId": "ecdc356da6a04743b34557692ce277fb"
            },
            {
                "option": "+UHh5NCRcrJ6ioVHri5KwNVTdPLNFny+buAgRwSQ48w=",
                "optionId": "cfcd60687d2a4754ae8b25424f418d63"
            },
            {
                "option": "52HA/3453wtZ1jsCwrHWvuKdb77B4HKFYiamSCcjOOM=",
                "optionId": "9b2502092da8480a9a8d613f0e6ad2e4"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "9106cb17d795498297268ded499cf543",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "jXe8QyU2awp8daL8NYvrzynuTWkPdaqaiZft8ORHrWDINAZ5FWwPMdhtBbdBx2+PRBLscHw3PyPXHlvzE11LTw==",
        "questionId": "c5eed63125554c62b7a54a7767d3e1ec",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "2gpHUSoFBA7IP6Lw8/HKJfOtF9MbF35XjCrBu9Oo7ok=",
                "optionId": "b32b3e7669d24afca86796622d09c24d"
            },
            {
                "option": "nEdlr4HPKkHxJnA3mJtQpboGPvZZ23mZu82Hpx7XJJg=",
                "optionId": "fc4d1f45ef564da09c9cb357b95bea2e"
            },
            {
                "option": "EPAnrHW/lKY9bxe89ngpCEyXRgUtf82e92XESdcT0Yc=",
                "optionId": "1ef6e9b6c239436a8e8b923aab3938fb"
            },
            {
                "option": "tjUIrCdx6DKtCroI9qy3tP/eF187heFmMEBMv1fLH0I=",
                "optionId": "07245bb1afd642c0bf7a78754026cafd"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "1ef6e9b6c239436a8e8b923aab3938fb",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "5RHCHzGo/4fXiyWFUPFHNoIFUc7Pyr9KjcPC7XOkEsFC74kgB72QGxetPKw7A4d0SVyCdlTeJcILCw3P9KlQDOxTS1ToZxCroyJXwmhByBdOkQ4AhPeEiVSfXmTHCIgECkmM2R8sjbJZGOtqZPHJ7g==",
        "questionId": "a7299481762249c38a7e6fad289d4b20",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "PrBJ/Gm8bsHnvL0HUmRxUc+kwyMFWZ6JhNVhPG2jHIE=",
                "optionId": "36d002b916ba4128ae14afd2c36d7c46"
            },
            {
                "option": "chab3yCJTRfG0I65/FnnmOrZvIWhUWFE+kM7TeT/DDI=",
                "optionId": "e5d04abf47b14ae88f76ef3a7b0581f3"
            },
            {
                "option": "vfWrP0r3egOjV6P3/wPo6WGintEHufAGiRfGkAk3dXk=",
                "optionId": "fa44537cc5c24450abe5f01abb4ddb3f"
            },
            {
                "option": "EVi+d4GITSEJfOL6rUnknFwYBopu2u+tscdV9Ob7po4=",
                "optionId": "81aa3a586ffc4f5da0e3471b946ff6e1"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "e5d04abf47b14ae88f76ef3a7b0581f3",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "uq63N2P3KmZP0OQKIQQCD6fvKNTIh3vmtHqj/3eqVy6MLT8fNgldasATWcE1puetdYnTiDsGCu3DOWGkaOhWRArTqPyCrO0xo2bQjZQ8HTfnvMwCRznDy3YNLFqwSShX34elrGQwkp93kJBg2FzOxaZxtpZUEoCApV5Nckvta4ws2/VYWALupZ/T1rWpxwtXpGJJaiy58Fqa6JCj7JOb4V5JXINs7DzFqRW09oNXU8P5aXkSIM+/rnci1B0OMG8F",
        "questionId": "e36460bfbc7c44f7b0c7766651db8ca5",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "e+wPzYVJYOUnXuSrZ86BbBDjyB0ayYJhbMreBJjXLvE=",
                "optionId": "54a00dfed4db4de7b2b0226132c2e07f"
            },
            {
                "option": "yMMaYbc1fhkS8MmvsqCNfCQV0rbWFuCdnL0D0MaRKSs=",
                "optionId": "4345c89636884291a34e00c73d0f244d"
            },
            {
                "option": "u2nXyqK78Y3Mh6wuflWU9ieQpxm0I5y6+XlW/sgMSsM=",
                "optionId": "5652a6a522af46ac83cdd801655b446f"
            },
            {
                "option": "IldNPv912BFkKCLDeNIcvFWxBb895hkQYJ5Wf0kfeaQ=",
                "optionId": "2d459ca25dda4b76a115a47cc5e53c56"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "5652a6a522af46ac83cdd801655b446f",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "tJCumnXqFjmEFz71Y2eJfz+0e8rbjsFN99MuX29gCmFRrfLApvgTXkdBsBFLJqB5jo94pG0NUzkKY5NFfNwcHTO2m9BlglrD85DB+PPsNB4stNSZvYwvXtv+3jcYxDJNoFsMzsCsmZ76Pe4hdltMNvSV8h4uO+i6YvAQ2FRHH0SEpcJT6JD8JehNHKAJRJSmPxdHajzNZqoIoGDVVBADNb0P9Wo0lYIKvXKY81KYm6TiuK/HalNzkbz6BlHPYGMQ",
        "questionId": "7905dc8a65d64e04a4d9bd6908759a19",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "hYDidDf6Gw6y840PHrY9ALkH0p9t395qimCXUqrs+JE=",
                "optionId": "2c7a8fe3d0cf4c00a05d89b611b926d0"
            },
            {
                "option": "5LIwLSEFvg8oW3s0f48eg/29LxL/QCTxPjA62xmT9VM=",
                "optionId": "6bec525410f84ebdabc75efe03249470"
            },
            {
                "option": "8Lz4K1udfe2rdff94wkMtIXhlb8TnsGiRhoLspcMKa8=",
                "optionId": "51dd960d7b7042fab91f5d9f33ab95a0"
            },
            {
                "option": "bb9okS1/Ee0ee0Hhkk9kZKh+ewU9v5VEk3h8fWiPZpk=",
                "optionId": "8a56513a1eaa483c832b5ed9f50f17b7"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "8a56513a1eaa483c832b5ed9f50f17b7",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "EEh5fX1DmRKE+RrcHT8Go6x62r1GslPFufr2Bf8BLalYmdkorIryNyl+RJu9CkRQiCHWYwxoSjGwdxSQT6no5w==",
        "questionId": "9dea9879b90f4ab7b212c3a4db3f50fa",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "rra9qBTqVwMeD9LKz4K0uCc98YDA7nYVIy14GZjMk1A=",
                "optionId": "2d20dc823a8a4222bfa5c8bc5a4f8fe6"
            },
            {
                "option": "zJ9nsP+lPlgjT2XdoVNzle8iIez/+CUUzjy+4rtfEL0=",
                "optionId": "7e42e1daac3444be9887561f41083837"
            },
            {
                "option": "4fhJjxE65MSI/JUOHsMVSQ2KEp/NXyw9RDu7tZ+hJXc=",
                "optionId": "6204d0212ad046f4912bf23fe8687b8f"
            },
            {
                "option": "vJ6ck02I1ZXQEF36fgxln+N3seO+85SiE0IbIAsLRXA=",
                "optionId": "5b340d9a9fb646708fb45ed2d37ced5c"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "5b340d9a9fb646708fb45ed2d37ced5c",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "qFT2TXpkISlvRkjoHFVKw2ajJ+x/e/jdTBniJuvEwG3yi+D0oE/pm5bgZ4HIdE/lRzx7hjBIh/PQsgJrBBYGKw==",
        "questionId": "e5a8b29b037b448391c27670433b2012",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "j4jxIW8MMHz60r0/LoyACWGecUEuu4WJoABoeNbmcAo=",
                "optionId": "53191d5c7ee047cab7a322e647903296"
            },
            {
                "option": "18Sx6kB69CWQEWsN7gsDIc8uen5e1r5ItWiYEsU+J1g=",
                "optionId": "9ce1d86f6db040c78385a59ce986a5d8"
            },
            {
                "option": "eVnNi59V8gCZuWtJ4dgThD4+rJQrwlnNFWOcGxBcnq0=",
                "optionId": "00140887fda342f398f9901e7e7f3534"
            },
            {
                "option": "q2gZOcMqv3hxafi+8uNK1F22lrc90faEoC5wi7B0wY0=",
                "optionId": "b280af3508844204957d5bcd0e2f7f0e"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "53191d5c7ee047cab7a322e647903296",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "HO9xcms5w5hOpsg1ItQAj0U8M4nq5VPjvaHT6oQMjoWk5n1sLYO41YEkKm5+ovwgrViVUlI96OOaRz4LF+JKCm0ZLGD4wO5OvWX5/pBQLR9SyF5mkdBBU381i3EfHzElDIVzjlJVap1KNAF/t+L2DKi71I1zrIO/Q8ouYAUssKe5TAAnTnJATpNnLVz8Tb4L8H6JABDCtmJ9O1o/Jp4QDA==",
        "questionId": "a5c76364aef2452abb78390a7b0b35a0",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "wLArvXBqZMN7Ece1+hn407yjj+VwSJjBcTuCrQToE7M=",
                "optionId": "ce0d852e23704df6962d07150e869497"
            },
            {
                "option": "IES1+DjLGHeHPXZdoOtTNKlSXV4Vh9V4CDq7yA5b3bY=",
                "optionId": "ea74c56488074c5eb221b89089ba0278"
            },
            {
                "option": "wzN8PCh8odZ0RvGeunQwLjic/Bunzq7YdAgKH5NZ5eY=",
                "optionId": "e4bb2dd963de45f2ac407cb09a45180c"
            },
            {
                "option": "6766Zo/J4Tgd1op6Ao24GhRFXSAUYwNTsy3dg14Qnwk=",
                "optionId": "4718009acba34366bd269d263a7fb01c"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "ea74c56488074c5eb221b89089ba0278",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "oG7dabK5XM5wpxs2/yjV6XrMuHsbhxYt9x1gDkjJOS6lnAKoYDOSB6BQwCvxE6B1RuIbLyl1IIO9KMYirsdlEQUrGA1y8c7dfsa0oLpMu0uVWaO/rNSoxArPGRMj5SWdOptykmaCqXAc1a+Y1m/9Htc7alEAwoR90zWRlFsV23Owwvbm/4LFlE4Ntpl/6VfmsB6s45zY7Yb2gY/4r1PdXQ==",
        "questionId": "b2429e081a7943b9a42ae8df6faf99c6",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "lVZ7bA88RdVHUHgonOv0HmBR3Z2oTLGlYumeoZkRBRM=",
                "optionId": "34e51b325dec4badb6f4eac834df25eb"
            },
            {
                "option": "X+1G4YbXevpwLSWGY1mNNQcDSyZE/akz/SNIg6E0AbY=",
                "optionId": "93d786e9e588458fa04cd3446a840b9a"
            },
            {
                "option": "WIvBIfKE6MDCfp4wxJLwR29yjrWtbUI2DmhIxlQxiDY=",
                "optionId": "ea3dfb10b4804d708703c22ee0eb952a"
            },
            {
                "option": "+keZQgmShxLezMKgpC0m0rvQEyaEKGk77TQ4RSHvzxE=",
                "optionId": "b852b51da9894ca7a189cdffca0fc7b3"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "93d786e9e588458fa04cd3446a840b9a",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "bpGdg12Xh4skKD+u8fRclpCu2dDgS/mDnGU7n7CUf+zqnIXY1nhcAeTJe1Zo+4YfGFqdw8t9RUWjTutTrcU9B7navOtJoAbv97rYQ9VbXVyQ+cpHwQrsm07kf2/iFExb",
        "questionId": "62ce10f986b348e39c6be5a8c1a7c7ff",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "Tq3Zp8//Dr/ovp2LFQxcSl5bIpIgZP/meLT9llsSXSA=",
                "optionId": "b83dc65494134a1fbeae996e653d309b"
            },
            {
                "option": "7VG5JOJVyjRr5fbceUJe9N1soJpVT6J9RjH6oBDjzaw=",
                "optionId": "45e2b94cbb2846d7a9563c65430fec4b"
            },
            {
                "option": "n7fmEerGHL8gylXHEl1cin0ZaXLWprrUsPsODLzIuRY=",
                "optionId": "da2472c090d5496cb24bf9553fb5bdf1"
            },
            {
                "option": "95CDCZEzr2JZWio+9SxzsYpoMb0khYT1/BW0NgoSrOc=",
                "optionId": "6e79b20da4a0449fb367debf0407d0d5"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "45e2b94cbb2846d7a9563c65430fec4b",
        "center": "IIT Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "oxJX+qLZwuAdw/bKnSo8E9v5bKkz+cQTil03551cNMAlu3RlmH4uHwOOpCjL8knVPNciqadJJfEgAXhV0/xJDWe/smBzHayMbrxAzZLimLPctZK4NYUbdmp/xsc/Nv2i4s/6JqdLgM1tHTbj7Q70YQrOHQH9ef9LCh2q3Cj1yyeWgx2fDswHQe4cLc4ly4zwFJnmn/t1ZDrjqq1kRzLb60sljUJ9oFP85kj7ooZAQeFZ2XRXq6CqmeuPmnt9D1asN9OI+/rUdLH3dNozhGIg2KpAk6rm/O03DSjCtgDXSECjIIbm1/avFEPdPL8xSeBQUdoEneOMhewlYorFJXygjjfqU8nQHrtS9CxTk56jtdH92518cBHxuUop1jPy8LoAsFNpXvoAzw67xXNYYU/0rXy2uXoY0s2kyAUoVPmYep/htfggoHbtoZV3EG+cyWoT",
        "questionId": "e6503a022f1f4c04a12e654e2a6296a2",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "3ys/vnm1T7itjrt59ZtTTvsrLJy8MH5Y03+RphhgyrI=",
                "optionId": "480451d0487b42c69eb5644188ed0f24"
            },
            {
                "option": "YynnBvh6j4bbr1golfy4lQTTnkYIYDOw3p5VbHsKGwA=",
                "optionId": "67b679cba9fb49b7850b3d54d09ecbb8"
            },
            {
                "option": "Ni/Nk9K1es+s0knddbZA3zi5w+xz5gWMnfWD/aQN6Y0=",
                "optionId": "42b962c7ea2a42cd89e8680a55217c71"
            },
            {
                "option": "F2dFXQqUqCPQd3mmruj7W75qd9mMki7ajhadVAFox5Y=",
                "optionId": "383297157a7849a1bcd4db8b862a67c4"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "42b962c7ea2a42cd89e8680a55217c71",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "bkfZhImYPkGodgNTYwyPoJjVtH03IEC5mYWZF/+/RWjWP4f42qqopzp/cF/14n0RlQGeymFHW8pMK851pylGiMegIPpKPVQxYbd/B+k029Eyn95ZcHojtUYIz5NFlsE2",
        "questionId": "edcdf6d6c6514aca8e329d047e5c4154",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "jRGxZ1pCZZlnYrSixFr7hCy/ukZrw2imCvm9jD24PCg=",
                "optionId": "f76a9ca5e10c481a861e625dfde173ef"
            },
            {
                "option": "wA6Xyzh7IauAaWdHvjT/g0WHiTva/VzxjDpfG5ivyZM=",
                "optionId": "854e12d13127447da2da00ca8e9c9f7d"
            },
            {
                "option": "/f+UvEnhR3kD/rTcXs3tpc80CCWw9+IMbC7+VGLmzfQ=",
                "optionId": "59c6191b9d204d1e95f4347d3fa76b9a"
            },
            {
                "option": "/mk9xUEH2cH/ErHj5FILi9KUFDkjJPo8vttPB6TWlo0=",
                "optionId": "2d808a7b837448c1926cbdb4cc10ef81"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "2d808a7b837448c1926cbdb4cc10ef81",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "fr7/MtTN7x3CHlYnDO9zrmsxiIU42rDR7jmpF2ERzU0B+o3rNc+oDltcVw6ZPOLV6g/6Wa9M0N22tyTPd73dCUoOCFdA2WEnAu5EvEYcBOxxEflMOpm9ouPD1XKm+gZaaBG1KaSDu0cpUvqnlTs++cRrlBDCbLANIbUiaiqd4Lc=",
        "questionId": "6970d1030b2a42908c9c1993bf92d6b4",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "X2608569PkoxKLYWx1G6xbInrh/IKU7BQ+vn8QRAHdE=",
                "optionId": "f193cd4d3450431c9415245c3efe625e"
            },
            {
                "option": "gPp2eQjCAQJC4VTlFHTW4svzg5+RBTvzT/d9/ydiXsY=",
                "optionId": "be86ffdbd7af46fea31e5d31d66f4ff3"
            },
            {
                "option": "QMLutt6AxS9gX4dYJtHb/iWNeW4kBqc8OxnFzQgWu38=",
                "optionId": "598cd2cc27a04064ae115be59e5113b3"
            },
            {
                "option": "YwHxntrRzr0rbO8vRortw6Ood49g9bEoMx9jtxVVWYg=",
                "optionId": "1cc63968671d4469885d20c50e533435"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "be86ffdbd7af46fea31e5d31d66f4ff3",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "6cBc+dYMecOGHIA2gAuLjD0FEcy+wpkDKXaiSq49hgrRhZfkjUDJZLZGsS4FLboT15CjC+nosAYs93mTco9n/tq3TKdtMjL50eZts3i5Qe1JsixbyG5bDNHP92glEB1OcthaiBgqDwRrYIC/zFVDFw==",
        "questionId": "d74e925058d94bc08b9a35d91dc49ea4",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "4at66uawpCGxvUiIEhVvpKazvpwQKF9DWwwp5BM1PXM=",
                "optionId": "06286e5a2772421483afc271f4ec489b"
            },
            {
                "option": "5per5Td6mEZDYmOSeEDWzVRwQRYsem/xtKG3MIN5W+4=",
                "optionId": "5c23ada9064e4bdcb3ed34e0ec82d56e"
            },
            {
                "option": "cPd/Z7bc3g0Y3876LTayo4ZD2xadwEAJE4XzYu2mgRc=",
                "optionId": "84eac6b50b684fd3b4c1576dd3666d3b"
            },
            {
                "option": "T2BnX0ZARrEPLOhkJaPOllkIFnmm9EhaGCDedFeixfg=",
                "optionId": "3ce2dc6f5f0347ddbcb84983522fc5e9"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "5c23ada9064e4bdcb3ed34e0ec82d56e",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "SzvqG5XwZ7pXPZ/AeKkOpyObRs4CpSGvkmppCbQ/j+yAEIJ0XDwfTo24tRHlfNeN4fGSrh9U+EEbaVhlgWDA4QoR1mZ8h53JsHNhzeyI3js=",
        "questionId": "18bcbdd8830e48d98e18645796b8ef11",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "sImpPUdwbm7LCNitbrVvE/SatDHP/fw8BRfrAWWoXXk=",
                "optionId": "f7d6330a99b24de3b225b792f7427068"
            },
            {
                "option": "goSXAJSDFqfA5QIZ/za7saWA/kt3qK3We/Ac8LOMkAY=",
                "optionId": "ae125f1087b746e5a1702bd6f29128a0"
            },
            {
                "option": "pj0UdYPrhlV/PwaHHR+R3ZChMDXBUaCb2VG9prF0FX8=",
                "optionId": "9cd99216a21f4105883aa30d73fa716f"
            },
            {
                "option": "lj/LgnN9e0dWJxEmPK1n//l++d+luvgXdQwOERN+X9o=",
                "optionId": "38b40bfb31494e1aa67cf3e9ec0eab46"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "9cd99216a21f4105883aa30d73fa716f",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "/mDV7h5HNkxQUQdH/Cv3dxcbTBVPEWuQ2YASvvBYR4r8g2vxrk1jJuLLwc6Jy9MVztLRuvCPMjicReqHebam/lrdy65gdZFafHgVBvz6tkG1V5JqzW8kWy7tfiB+xtCPG2ypGfhDs1Vu6OwXk7OGUA==",
        "questionId": "d8712e33c59f497eae21bf88bf12b56b",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "+vDG3dgKBxKMrXIqBf04plsf8UOAs8eJVkozQToQWZ0=",
                "optionId": "8a4db639b8f74aa4a522ac9fafa99095"
            },
            {
                "option": "uf6pRAI6BD62jYw7l3LAGGO26/nDTjTCRhYDzW+hZ3E=",
                "optionId": "1b0a0d5e8dc745938c2539cd01f0df91"
            },
            {
                "option": "gFpS62IdnYfTB9OnRZLh2MWVc9WWar/c/XSFhN2INMk=",
                "optionId": "66f0d2b7534a4b79b30e7f07b58693ad"
            },
            {
                "option": "jukBhOdwwCwYvmkLOCp4MEK0oND+/ESXI93xwMAQmhQ=",
                "optionId": "a3ab68b718254089b19b99baf280c88a"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "8a4db639b8f74aa4a522ac9fafa99095",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "8Mw/xeWoRijcOOdYfOqFlikrta/QjyXn0Uwu8iBrJS5nnsolWVYiBow+PgCYN/2CBqBpctgXQEXF4pAohQWRSQ==",
        "questionId": "9dea9879b90f4ab7b212c3a4db3f50fa",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "RThCPtsUzalfNHtJle7mlijxp6X8xNaspPoGHFLns8Y=",
                "optionId": "2d20dc823a8a4222bfa5c8bc5a4f8fe6"
            },
            {
                "option": "RXMiDri0F4IeLo15D9/5IvQ/4Uf5DupjBjx029E0VnI=",
                "optionId": "7e42e1daac3444be9887561f41083837"
            },
            {
                "option": "V+Is8vPPNMXQP8WUtZKQrPwi1RRa89If4N6fr9B7krE=",
                "optionId": "6204d0212ad046f4912bf23fe8687b8f"
            },
            {
                "option": "rLldk4To8+Zjnkm/iUrnsu6lUi1pd5MM8X91KEXfiGU=",
                "optionId": "5b340d9a9fb646708fb45ed2d37ced5c"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "5b340d9a9fb646708fb45ed2d37ced5c",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Uu/A6NqVHLw+UaZLAOTt56cY1RgmXQUgJloY3/bw6BFiRCJ+6iwAEcVUJhGaHjskZVGBih6rwRb/RjAoYg1/10rHQqpJCXTdMqSKu6HkTYBhRCcOo94f+9J+2ko51QufPrnPi9+hTOkHoK9bCR2575ZbblqJ2JGt5FMimIW8yvOaCNgi4SeF76gzBaoZjkWCFO/QULCWTrNqbLnTtv0zrVnqvI7eI0fXlVeVdbd7PRmrTInLiqrdIXs1CJGqcn1ahdkgD09uIXYNfl7jrCGpdh75ZzkAaFf9HWVfUq3Ayo8YP+Ch9btdf+NyuU5eUORGjN5VnVZJZZ01FR2wLP1BKhlPUnMmJAoF4n5GFqIsUcjc5uvE4k9tLW5auU86HY7haAHjJgsQiWWNVF4PCQif+Wx0GrAdbKEq2QUo8daPRFTbv/5lRdVB79Xrexc7Biov",
        "questionId": "5caea09e9e04423f8253702374c24bc2",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "tf2mhdC6241/Mx/j0X4m9SPOMw781Q+JgyGMgWJqbNo=",
                "optionId": "227fc1923d1c47d5aef1667acc0e3b43"
            },
            {
                "option": "HKLaLQ2yXLlJCaK4S6RzHHF7JAAgNHIG3xE9Rpkoj7w=",
                "optionId": "6d836bc71f6c4533bb788ce263411f59"
            },
            {
                "option": "EYH6DYWTMqJeRvcNxC3xGRJklmO4S2Gqt9h6VSYLR/A=",
                "optionId": "f26b50e701f4441784374a14fd0ef266"
            },
            {
                "option": "unaU4BlrX/k6yj+ttxnhP0R9jj6fRt40Y8DEmYyOCLk=",
                "optionId": "d470d0c1089b4982bcb70be10387c409"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "f26b50e701f4441784374a14fd0ef266",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "BYsG6ovAGLxDiqKmtPIwtPvy++bWNvVD16MFLRMXBEGoKnntvH/w1sImrUNGP/zmbU+EOe7weZ7ywF6OGp6bug==",
        "questionId": "8e3238d6ed474a64ab18150ede22d666",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "P+E01iHcBPQScApUJacUABZ1PlHe+WqqcQfwn4XqVVo=",
                "optionId": "5f64a212389f405e81660c7aa7af4502"
            },
            {
                "option": "ylGrnA4rF7pZjcTAHwFErtzLyrkWN2lnUQ4reKgZsSk=",
                "optionId": "7ae34ff1fe4e4160afc34b5b5d33f1aa"
            },
            {
                "option": "aDQVIt9ggSHkZOjjoz0WHWZ7cfL2+ahU/fYuzrUIy6c=",
                "optionId": "b15e5f687fde45728af6ad9113bf3da1"
            },
            {
                "option": "F1RiijcXKyhmNbBk+4qguGk7J8ctTejySRZ7O++aOFY=",
                "optionId": "26a5e035fe564338b12c20bcb95cf9b4"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "b15e5f687fde45728af6ad9113bf3da1",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "tIc19wYw8LxSrMWNrY0tbz9ZLui0BcoAqDz+qprKxnh+M3sut8o6Y16IZ5OqiWaanbXw75s+f9/dTHhfCtUnOjWgDddBFETMtJTueQvY3ZMh2K/u4oNfVhVE3nNkxdNH344R3orsiT8w41DSyqGsX99iOUSxDcB9wCo32ofd54grem9NwjKltzkCaUzFtSKCfYkctUxEybErSZvoHwA8CIri6qkk2ktruIyXgA4d9w05gDQ2IWteeS/ABPD7Oa7ULSxj7On9MsQnmIPKrD+1/Gwmv9rJM7gQN1hmcCQnKFI6Y4tOsRr6nTpwNWcS73mmTfpf2b27v/Lvpqjwwpmw8Y/cX6ccIt8xeI8W0v6JC8QXkIVyCilW4bmnrI2ynGxKCKRdcCxwbID9z+MIuf+bSjwLmeKiRydH4ufeBbpxjPjedOlG4FaWElPbVXuQui8j1N/HaGCeARRmdP1Dn6sW1w==",
        "questionId": "9ebbf4d4388c4b629e157af5748e5e16",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "VtHlvMX+VC5oZFbe1dWIlBHB2uufVqQLbwHMRQsFOSg=",
                "optionId": "d87c718e8524493ebc2c5e8504191406"
            },
            {
                "option": "XPsPh5/fOP7TI5J1s85N2m0KEKiTASgETKw1fPu4c68=",
                "optionId": "d830d30d5bb540abbb4c88a5e358fa54"
            },
            {
                "option": "93AKCacRKbklzIjt9fXUnPWgq/FsGHnq+LOpvSZ2Tn4=",
                "optionId": "3460d1f377164436b8986e12112e2e20"
            },
            {
                "option": "qxhbwr63ssZqqxpV/llJUO72aVyIB195z33yHnPwKwo=",
                "optionId": "153cde84c1ba4cb0a921cfb1c9bb47b4"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "3460d1f377164436b8986e12112e2e20",
        "center": "IIT Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "XWriO9E5LfqFvKKxTtaOg0KRPARmB85V+az39pqEwnapo7ewWH2S25+3vPhDLVaTahqInkJ4uS+o+nTNJwzSI+a/0v5pLqd49sKfzTIALJy7vsLVuuYQXkA9XGGKQRD8HZ9T073dttjTdRgszRm2LW56I9MSwXPaQTkpCrLU2SJolg4Fo+lkmKYMMqg0mwRrV2VjHwTaARAHWLfHRSLL+xnF9tGYB5InscPcpYZjZLi6wk8PrZ0KuC2FT3xd0y4K4bwlDVCMUUBu9aDkwtXk+Q==",
        "questionId": "c8a9bf5d39f844928c59dd50c1bf8cd2",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "IBWwmhwUa8+LmfFEW7US5yNsiCemr77BBFTi9+3zFcU=",
                "optionId": "450a8791c19a4269958c5d05d5141118"
            },
            {
                "option": "+hx9OxyKcO+FbqaIYcIX2WRQALJb/6h4JO5zhfo+K3Y=",
                "optionId": "3ddcb96a35b14838bfec9944fca65348"
            },
            {
                "option": "OFEPpyOKmOL4Uun0V+Uqc+rq0rAXfi7YQ/ONp8r0xm4=",
                "optionId": "eefdce2d1eb5491a867317936514ca4e"
            },
            {
                "option": "s2sr44Rr4FPkXXl+u8Q0eHdqQ3rRMqBr+1XW18/7u2I=",
                "optionId": "e1de7ff93c4540a48f92e54949c454ce"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "e1de7ff93c4540a48f92e54949c454ce",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "fYQHH1SDsei21Jn8bJBMrLf2/dTYnxvv7VDigdRx0RYSiXDHuivzbG2OL721Zlciic1rvUwtxJUX+uwsGcDEstdbaoVWjCYVuTxOIOG7/7BarqoPA7O/hlY3L8Qc49SoBk6eRU4By1PtJN6hLX03sRvVQP1z0EuTdwW5ETAUWCKzOb4HwkcU95MVw9ETToSWrZeqv56ROm2aoLgrt7QAkIQCayBCB8yKoixLXLeYAk20fJy/dJa3CTun1Nz69+n8Px/wd5+ya+kRjXLhNWTQzAa4xhNxzCDYk0sk7xJ7LEJDMjgSJS1EK1n8u/vjULgR84EkW+5NXuzBTKhu8Kk8G3ZstxlmCjaEihzIUf3nkT4LvckoEkMg4JvaicT6taSElwsFZg4GvoS0t7eg47q6HUcBYPqIxLp85jCXXAwFSTU9E1uB5p/x3VBKCVFpyeGc",
        "questionId": "e6503a022f1f4c04a12e654e2a6296a2",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "mut2F0gUMVkRg1zKT+w/gf+sZMxTGglN7YbE+tlY71k=",
                "optionId": "480451d0487b42c69eb5644188ed0f24"
            },
            {
                "option": "ttWAyW1rabUlDuHyU9Ggdaoz2IGsVpHE6Zqlsm89eng=",
                "optionId": "67b679cba9fb49b7850b3d54d09ecbb8"
            },
            {
                "option": "XQ4HjWir2gPSIpESTNPVkFU9jlO7WPchfOaU1SgBseo=",
                "optionId": "42b962c7ea2a42cd89e8680a55217c71"
            },
            {
                "option": "Xkf3Sl6B3AM4xJaoxQTaVOIlDnMeaPLzVn5wwGszMXk=",
                "optionId": "383297157a7849a1bcd4db8b862a67c4"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "42b962c7ea2a42cd89e8680a55217c71",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "EY+lKxWoxgXEfYVzoeE2DetmkAs5NgEZWvgsOYgd4/v7Hh28nzwlROkewcIglVYjRJftREoImQNaoN05n3UHYlDJE2so60/T1PVd9WLhm4teDXJpjDOI1fbmWQ7nlE0iJihPitO3BrR63fDOlar31mHafE+4mZGDw4ZNyyzON8VpOgWPy4dI7gJyrgF9kpCpBg1aYCbK556TkLViaCOle5X3hfps9Ty/ZcYpkK5GCinxHyqVv+YPpQyGbrKm13SuiwkI16vP6Nsk4uChuch1IjfXObxn25JUZAKLuSuJy66iOK5KfvJTb/BYfNnRBsjkDXRjQ6t/EMHWvEIKOfGVeobbzvyq0AiGO4AXeIIrXvAnRfo0IUXjL5NUjisy/K4bgReYKw/J6ZXuEH6/GfOem5SJI0VvcPJkEuSg5HwxCOpv5/jYjbXBgL7L36w7L7AI",
        "questionId": "e6503a022f1f4c04a12e654e2a6296a2",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "VQX6cIX236zOtcWeWbLVOOeNTY9XjLl3Han7FFWzbYs=",
                "optionId": "480451d0487b42c69eb5644188ed0f24"
            },
            {
                "option": "WJYz1XfWXRhlt8DouRYZIl4DvV0/x9RbT3tLoKVUW4I=",
                "optionId": "67b679cba9fb49b7850b3d54d09ecbb8"
            },
            {
                "option": "Xbc5a7flJ01Y/tqfmlsyXxqlNTIqu47DVdhnSB9jm8w=",
                "optionId": "42b962c7ea2a42cd89e8680a55217c71"
            },
            {
                "option": "QWfNCRd3KCvKNIF1eKwrGRQuZ4oRhqDo2VFkeejH4hs=",
                "optionId": "383297157a7849a1bcd4db8b862a67c4"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "42b962c7ea2a42cd89e8680a55217c71",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "1yf/4uo3SKc7OGf1quT5t1LntQDXa8AHUvgIz/GimwGzCGfOJvBVFBb90V++OfOSTYEthWhE79XDoEi4CQGQaETgeL8a1fUvvnC1LJkiLnb0tdwju5eCFfobYVJCcTvb7wLCHAaUYb9GZK3ElweZn5kRyMw6wvn22JY8CLiFMR6XhY5Vqdd6YcVyo0IlpwDl1JbkdMTRY8Ab1RMBaaOXHo0moGzKoDlVrgtHals2F0kKQbFDFM9/zcNT+GbZ9cw0Z3Hc3wiafKsxZYqyDUpwD2xeaudNaydZwb5KUAJM/oRc7nn3mfLUd9yqDrElEM6HnGGDKAtssP3JS8K7JNLUOExDKkPIZNvh0PXt9JBAODfO3wsHUg9T1MLfXmG1sxWd2XaAhEqy3LhYS4eIk9Lmbr1+e65SKG8i+zrtoskRzwirVjwMF5uCgUCpMz5PGM9TV3OuBhpaRwEhDNrPgfeJzWbTpPjsMnykpgwD4RwrxFPdKSJKU6W5q9yw4oUzm934C4Zh01Zhova7viw0a/kz0Ys/LcokF2QArST3svjouxU=",
        "questionId": "756a99da72ee429c8c681e67cd49ed50",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "4L9o2aus/Z789/tPhjvxOfJEsn7rv6X7EJMzNKOvdkU=",
                "optionId": "40c535f201054ecbbecd8c4480ad906f"
            },
            {
                "option": "5z24p51ZHaL04pjyY/asHb+VEV9RVov75/cZDC/m52Y=",
                "optionId": "706d7487914d4fd6afcf6ab45cb312e2"
            },
            {
                "option": "tA8Fh1EOLF3z2H3zVuz2YWtvGJtb6i298VlXvuf8AhE=",
                "optionId": "c04fa4bbdaf44f1b8e2fcdff17a7a211"
            },
            {
                "option": "XxmhqlCEFLJQu58IqkseRp+OO3qzTOfL/N+RNiI1jOc=",
                "optionId": "c803f639d286415ca697cbc4b1a1a99f"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "40c535f201054ecbbecd8c4480ad906f",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sw2lV9jrbJBWLFx5bIAZrC7VBG1z2+XJVAGWdWVPkcuRlkSE5JwzSRWtRzq4qSZmGNvUWkhsRKO8B+7E19o1ZQ==",
        "questionId": "8e3238d6ed474a64ab18150ede22d666",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "RW8tFJqCGn7ZEDorAFYk8Hf4p1/4UX+fstPcbwclASg=",
                "optionId": "5f64a212389f405e81660c7aa7af4502"
            },
            {
                "option": "6FOkKQ+aodAvsajrJGt22JGRHdVa1V6AqGxNC97U3kA=",
                "optionId": "7ae34ff1fe4e4160afc34b5b5d33f1aa"
            },
            {
                "option": "sjvx1lyyIl/m5/++CjW1cF9w0bSfoI2loSEzGgB9OEQ=",
                "optionId": "b15e5f687fde45728af6ad9113bf3da1"
            },
            {
                "option": "ThQCF7gh6upNfKYReuZZpdRxix7EycQ4YmGp/lYJnE0=",
                "optionId": "26a5e035fe564338b12c20bcb95cf9b4"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "b15e5f687fde45728af6ad9113bf3da1",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "08vorRLm71zNWa4oq3si6oLwiZxJEb6Ri43EQRCixWa7lqAJVUDA4PJ3TvaL23ENnKSg1Q2rnWuFylJYwh7xmIj1qV8oPJMyM9HcaDFf9LV6n3oIFdnr/2txyN1gcet4TfLXGIlQf/LBNK8uwvsWuA==",
        "questionId": "27d5d31e71c2480faf03fd17191d19fe",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "fZ22MoOVDNGzAMZ3auh2JNsykr8Zm8kqTm9qdsql3BU=",
                "optionId": "8017a33fb9084e9facaae4d0ff4608e3"
            },
            {
                "option": "f2jUMfV51nk9Pd1pWBt4dV5WL/5f86FLik3AltUNpyc=",
                "optionId": "1b3b40666719414d8e69243dfa069ccc"
            },
            {
                "option": "F7ovlY/h82MtGdMBE/mKOrukyHM0tmdjieyB2/U/cls=",
                "optionId": "a68b737dfbbe4ff1bd6f29c02326dd45"
            },
            {
                "option": "Esec4wN9eYj6YAj+0Wsb+PeBhATHQJPep1U4yAIgsx8=",
                "optionId": "5ffcd66a27c4455782630450572b9b00"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "a68b737dfbbe4ff1bd6f29c02326dd45",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "y4IojSfE46KSagwherbcYndafrAEjH7UzjMEkc3wkUyH4e6+BVzVUmcEHMZJm1n4jwRwfDVnscwnzWoqd7gFGWNINz9+sVsjiSjSC4gp3OLcpMICQByLF1UFpFLjGgOiICN8d+Y0Gtco4MbrMoK0CM7454Bo+nkvsozZJZYP4b55z9P3s1K1HC3KKlcxP1dX311eIxAj5+dtIMw3b9Z9x1HMLqZYIiCLpbvbIgIQsoItOB4MZ/DhC96IaAkcv8w6K3S5/hMkgyh+6Tchyi2xKw==",
        "questionId": "55a74e62c40e4a6b9da5a41f1125ae68",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "WdsWuDEbHdkhMq0Vpj8ow0IrjbduqtUgoLXq09Eh6mk=",
                "optionId": "c0beceb496ee4581b419f463f13a91c9"
            },
            {
                "option": "HMpk8XioTuORYHD814HcbUtPxnYcr6PeTqNPy5xWTTk=",
                "optionId": "1661f2155e8544e2a626de701d89fa37"
            },
            {
                "option": "D0YRcCDJl1smaMDt+1/re+zBdWC5L+wrqSYCx/VXfQU=",
                "optionId": "659bdd21d3b94b19992a1da773c22c14"
            },
            {
                "option": "N5BsaEhWf1uPl3qJWz74wfb8JMf5wV/cv3v5jcA6KBY=",
                "optionId": "7cf0dd4fd1e641ed8a3505cea3a9e40a"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "1661f2155e8544e2a626de701d89fa37",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "KFYi/pw1nABdOE+tgOPbIftMKdHnccgsYjhVhwgicUUfPUAB1Ael4nwhdrhjjuEvfFOz1+YkCqNN2mDYBGRDy7W/qheqJYoiut6wMKY3Wxodl7S+RSuTGUWsEpxU5u/fCNUDSDQwjaCG7xiUGkE/IPdTwiDyesjYhhlRaLtcAus=",
        "questionId": "ae10018a09df4a309fab8f15df780c60",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "OcfNkHxJIUgvTVW1nfe7luVoKgkgSBM+NkZXomZ7t48=",
                "optionId": "2adecc2237134b34aa0b1d4a51a5345d"
            },
            {
                "option": "OEAqFE/u8bBD4aPLmMrCRydMWP4QlwB9+1u5d/hefQQ=",
                "optionId": "72ab02b35a5745ad86ddf57e924409d5"
            },
            {
                "option": "QH7s8cW/NtwtmBdasM7TxweUK2dYDvDpvO5h6Hyws1I=",
                "optionId": "6946b3998e5e465d88e24d9ecacef260"
            },
            {
                "option": "gJjKZwAaM7vuODGkhRo/vrAU0Ivm05t47ZMJpy+TxbI=",
                "optionId": "f08dd5f6131c4680947f69c281a88bc9"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "f08dd5f6131c4680947f69c281a88bc9",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "+3eCFLSxGscMOqWu4FaMHftHQaPpHQILLNV4yc+n1JUInqYbomtu18dWwCFdVYk6qvEHXygDTCCaf/NgWPsSbMl8I0PFhBR2UQviSYFnSnirL/8gWWw7TDjse+xyb7GODAefSNFYpowhgdSQDLvUCRilv4arC6ruf4BEcwDSJlMd9xBH2yGW4Y1ZZkmSsq94WeBqWiCCXaS6rhpWCmsOU+t2HqlDNjlMqxgmq3PUdrjFDivn8jgEyH+uGxIx+IqvH6uHtM7Q/kTGQcWFSIPJA2jVK53EcFfgFH9H7g6Wrw2Pg+GDzBfiuRzuhLNv4HrkGPT91ilF9Y7Elu6S/VqfCQABrUr5gOepwq/CLHM5NoGpPEVazeOELEKwJs7husfcAMmAUj2XrvGFL9F+Cn0o2ZbS0wmZ5ndu8W2yvJdKv88E/+QPkYcyzYyV9G9WlpAMPNRA4iXJ+08pkm+HIeSRVQ==",
        "questionId": "62367569bd1d491b89f24faf861c6559",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "dy9brdcpIbrOc/RSfZ9ddCub7QLNPEJjk6QX/37o1OM=",
                "optionId": "9bbaae8c96cc47bfb833e0f9f2f8b856"
            },
            {
                "option": "kPmBTWreLzvOfwqpCGnPpoKS4kwhLYZmknWgG+s0iHo=",
                "optionId": "3827b7abfc5345d9bdcb93ce01fae1e3"
            },
            {
                "option": "Wjxa+Scnq2JvMZkzKZKyxr8F/UsTxyYC1BHb9VQR5jc=",
                "optionId": "c0f1e6f40e1244968903342e36d1ec80"
            },
            {
                "option": "Y3gPkMNwKdcO6R1evpHiBFgLPVLt/K67MLBCMEJo5ko=",
                "optionId": "575c73aadd07453a8ff40bfd2d80a980"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "9bbaae8c96cc47bfb833e0f9f2f8b856",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "YS53zVmsEdpou34jwGGxRTfoJl0nWlKyxxh5wt+SDupazraa5fkGjxl1xz9E9XoEmOh46KWoOULVbIXvmOEid4V+09OXrCJGEH/YLdffvdjUxkxdEZNK+VmODdirEDx3i87hzrZbaqd7l+KdYh/UG5WrMj90xxqqvHLomqcePsSb4sZ/lgAqpBG1lDe03SL5Dabvgwya/a6A8IHpFE00Sf1qAe1JSZDhgyJWaFyNfpIq+YXiirs0vkwDh0ZS4T0jEKf5VgA2hHiTuQ5Bd3mFPg==",
        "questionId": "f3773d8b4e5b4f96888dd56a437dfee4",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "qhyg/1hywIoeZHoqA4XozDNgD04gvKIQpRRSl9hSpUE=",
                "optionId": "a0831fd6a72945bd9be0d9087eead0f9"
            },
            {
                "option": "DNvHi090D6tCz3pFV/NxuyHLoe6pMPpGEV/Ro1rVOw8=",
                "optionId": "a9d4d8370b8440d2b94d11abd198e747"
            },
            {
                "option": "S+EnWm0yNHqj6BeSi/8hDxJXW8cLK9q9Zn6GlRrbOow=",
                "optionId": "d9ec79e57c624b70a61765ff9ac12500"
            },
            {
                "option": "AFavMg9R5TQuedLyaGRhbyzayaF0U26ePjiZIyxLh8Y=",
                "optionId": "85eca15f6d02443db755784ce650b5d8"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "a9d4d8370b8440d2b94d11abd198e747",
        "center": "IIT Madras"
    },
    {
        "question": "l7nVQLj8qRfPtfX/wC21HJZB4XXaUsUC1nnr4yUhaqPi8iKDVa3lKxHvWoMMM2NuyEf9+ne/r73wj9sKkz4puKmXTqSox1AjKRTEZnnwo5mxhF0wxqGo2qF/cN84U2AvsCV+Vm129sxvrHhdldp66q6oVVe1GGY9oseVoSAIlGXAp3r39t4flfEPNX1nRNQp1kAAgn2Cpv08EypCR5qMMUgqkaN88e/vRy8b18Egok4/jaioQUuisuUPLRMQIzrqnev6mDbpmwddR1Zd6teZVgSalS8hWnxR9YNHEDjI0/l1C49xUfw6tZJKsIcUa1i2yvBFqRIVV2mIJYb7CTqREcUIzgaZC9Pjnud5xZWuZjoETsdbvTkqQ18cvCmFtl4+G+C1F7Q6D1SmwzT5zRAwwhHFT95+BF9T45yOJuKHiY78tQVUQ6KHxcfKBnSctmj/eVLQ0LcwTQZSj0UQbkNOq+5r2Pmk9xGM8WwoPmNFXoUIbbjRkqmgHcsicKbQu2CiX2tXYra0Tn9r57P/VBfGonH0qpN5x6Q+yG3S3ZRwcCc=",
        "questionId": "756a99da72ee429c8c681e67cd49ed50",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "CC6vjkSjbMgbZGnzaYUo1y3C3JlI9zCuPvkJDrG70LU=",
                "optionId": "40c535f201054ecbbecd8c4480ad906f"
            },
            {
                "option": "NFlbg2a8Yr2pxVC1pNHV8ZGfl2XuJ7FBu5gN00NAS/Q=",
                "optionId": "706d7487914d4fd6afcf6ab45cb312e2"
            },
            {
                "option": "VAfS7lTuUQM06EfF0+OleJtn4WMTS2wTAhK0Bw69Wog=",
                "optionId": "c04fa4bbdaf44f1b8e2fcdff17a7a211"
            },
            {
                "option": "Z0WL1xNarxmh94z/I9LqWEMY+1iu2X5XNSnAzappO0I=",
                "optionId": "c803f639d286415ca697cbc4b1a1a99f"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "40c535f201054ecbbecd8c4480ad906f",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zg7pBB+Cqxfj4sIAlh4UMfCdRlVLKwqbs7UhESCj4uPKymaN1A17ChPFeV64FStFkgd0jIVrY+u2/6e4N/8qd36lmkp2zrbMD5q6NuXOnKnBY2KijSwfB/60jTaxcxkDjUd4eTNDv+2RE8smC5Jo52fH+/2jW0o+td3RS8mpZkHvp9rbab6bhaAnoiCC3Ssjw7MoDDiI89WbqVliVAcZgw==",
        "questionId": "0ab1c350dffb4752a9e08cd92f6be6b5",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "JKzOTcS01sOXLesE9nD59iJdWVZUDfMWrwGEF1W8Xro=",
                "optionId": "a85a6fedb3c2409dacf7e4398c816899"
            },
            {
                "option": "mepJoAJjVfGuth+N+0jA5IyubhTyG+DJNihrNRHiKT8=",
                "optionId": "162b284355f442f9be0424335c747bb3"
            },
            {
                "option": "1Iy2gqOObvrTghE050L1uVDg8Q+OOh1bb9KI27mHMxI=",
                "optionId": "a37155e13ded4c7780a904a2b9821f8f"
            },
            {
                "option": "hf/YYnCx4wsd2j4wxCWsyyw6iXYFyLHfGUMmuys2eH8=",
                "optionId": "8b05d986a3854e918e7647acb55ce66e"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "8b05d986a3854e918e7647acb55ce66e",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "K1bQW8Pp0EafVkQumkHXehp1Lm/jenX24sR30/wcvSAEnAxTnYYHya6qlf8SwEbzSl73AznTfWHaAwH5sy23Qg+WX67A6mIkNX3iUN0TiPv4pe6DUiK+Tfn1nVeyZcmNnjeFlQGoxu9hQcZDtnJ/5g==",
        "questionId": "d74e925058d94bc08b9a35d91dc49ea4",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "ykjoq4W8R7GGLF+Unsu8oBribqyn2bEPx3Q1Bf1fvCQ=",
                "optionId": "06286e5a2772421483afc271f4ec489b"
            },
            {
                "option": "Bs2F7s1oJSNqIaJnxHQDkRHxxC6HviL/iR89LGExtMM=",
                "optionId": "5c23ada9064e4bdcb3ed34e0ec82d56e"
            },
            {
                "option": "tSuFEJe/9dPJvv0KpxH6s7e4IZalb4Yc9Oa36vch0OE=",
                "optionId": "84eac6b50b684fd3b4c1576dd3666d3b"
            },
            {
                "option": "b8oZT0sdZy4/UscETPzB8E7jopePvq9bR/JCJCbW7Ls=",
                "optionId": "3ce2dc6f5f0347ddbcb84983522fc5e9"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "5c23ada9064e4bdcb3ed34e0ec82d56e",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "+wnepzZJ5UFlXPVDwwP2T0e40pwfmg3YemwwqWH3vtdDv+uzHTTmv1ElBO0EghsTbxm6sxaKEG/0pg4r9CnTxOF5cuugJgJC+xQsD47FvFgITRUHSJGbgX181KQkjcrh",
        "questionId": "62ce10f986b348e39c6be5a8c1a7c7ff",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "l3P16/hFRHoo4YHLQCIUztpTH6a8lD+zRHf3l/Nr0go=",
                "optionId": "b83dc65494134a1fbeae996e653d309b"
            },
            {
                "option": "pG5u7m3f5tuLwWDguHplawJoA8JPEpRrccTSZeggw/E=",
                "optionId": "45e2b94cbb2846d7a9563c65430fec4b"
            },
            {
                "option": "b4OiKUIrdE9y2paLjBflO4cL5q+iOE/U5BiX1ul8JOA=",
                "optionId": "da2472c090d5496cb24bf9553fb5bdf1"
            },
            {
                "option": "MOwN6rB7Gx+XIhVJDX7RWfiSS5c2HEpNlCtotTM+Cag=",
                "optionId": "6e79b20da4a0449fb367debf0407d0d5"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "45e2b94cbb2846d7a9563c65430fec4b",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "qc647GRevuoACxzd+kxJ3lceOgzUbLPPjumqcdi43FEgM2LVCv2Y5hwW7yPo4PtVPKywWQQF2vMzPwwuLx0TFPyMAIeFw7jBd55BMakIeuU6TzpuSsPP0N8nWilLxh/v",
        "questionId": "22e9641a02c844148f7a08b6057dfdf5",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "Cv2znL/XW881CPGwDzUPTemknYmOGi1QtcnMlH/v2ug=",
                "optionId": "fb887d9ab984484d9172dbfec9851e04"
            },
            {
                "option": "MvcE7EDk3CrNoTnRa+hKI2mBhwOx08t21MOzAyIc2/g=",
                "optionId": "01f94c9cb2f6438b8adccb8717c07ec0"
            },
            {
                "option": "rgqYSiFHpyKGkeCrcNbUAnY5jRUWF8Bie3Og7zXM6s4=",
                "optionId": "e27570e48ec84b5c9019fd86c952bd1e"
            },
            {
                "option": "ybpeLAoZUx4NCjEs6dXetvjoR8WwbwZGv63qNVzOhog=",
                "optionId": "cdf14a3420c847ceb9a0c3ac8e324e0f"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "cdf14a3420c847ceb9a0c3ac8e324e0f",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "7alogP0GHq6GehvyWmW2WqYk4+AgX8ZeRYEj+kCcBuvWMaSV2e6t+Zd/z+ABkAZBSBwJst8MGISnq+N5qeb0XVE9eRDrzEa6NDlWFDUVilnVbZSNsYPMYEr3kpTiV57yDFuCm3CZ0efBxfXYzjCpfgBJkbFrgFljlC6CrjUhPNLfkBVuWJp59uHfltOeW13ksUTjyBdFsOiVMrxZoBwWNQ==",
        "questionId": "0ab1c350dffb4752a9e08cd92f6be6b5",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "1kqip9xBWfmN6A1TBQA+fegFZ+9esQhe3nQ4vzkG6Lg=",
                "optionId": "a85a6fedb3c2409dacf7e4398c816899"
            },
            {
                "option": "j57hhaacf0uAxeAye0WcA36TUQ0ThODh+zqfc3W/370=",
                "optionId": "162b284355f442f9be0424335c747bb3"
            },
            {
                "option": "Ti3tyoVJm7kqUDHXZ389kV4SVnOFffl7WCCwFaMyC9s=",
                "optionId": "a37155e13ded4c7780a904a2b9821f8f"
            },
            {
                "option": "jTMl9Mn/+KEP8CV1hHJwQ2h29kRbdG1NiaN7TbHGmgk=",
                "optionId": "8b05d986a3854e918e7647acb55ce66e"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "8b05d986a3854e918e7647acb55ce66e",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "4h4Vf9Iu3RKk6bwR9NFvkqtZ6WHJhjOioDrbWMwPRHMZkddppxVb9Hi8f4Nv7ocAoQC9v3qVd5RRj0nFJAlSWBTSjU9ApoA6FQTjkcr7lezO95ZXeuiGtszOuihN19jb0gvXBbF4L9Vw6ypXW9H2FpSS4Q0a9Atr0yjND0PIP2ydIA2A8dLcRaQij1l3+UUENeRu12/jSUJ+7PrQcsGPuQ==",
        "questionId": "3d7abe02c6f049a389258c9f94c7fcf7",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "8qIU3vPsgTPTOvo+VvJxV1Q+K3Dlg8uftHs9N7vpb0w=",
                "optionId": "2ea69b52eb464326ade155c36007d330"
            },
            {
                "option": "/ixeUjk296bqmRipboCKsiNfM83pR1LIh9CEHRMIxcY=",
                "optionId": "f1ed6b9166b44ffba3ea08d8f17950bb"
            },
            {
                "option": "cCasoyRQbh0wO7Qa4zS+/e2yr7tlIDkRbG+FCoTAyb8=",
                "optionId": "7b46db36f791499fab2a764c04614c01"
            },
            {
                "option": "P02TXOJ5Tip5AUFHWa+38HpJgMfDGBlTeYhRN+apwnZEQk6hPW0nLRYAyk7+RnRS",
                "optionId": "0ca6ba6038cd4f3b8d1a1025db5df4b3"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "f1ed6b9166b44ffba3ea08d8f17950bb",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "zAawRQtguct9ZU/VoccvSOFa+nMgaonxGvJv7ahpPi/jbsIDEQ6EsToyhs7+D/hBdSMVe5sh6Y7ntEPPwWp64bXg5zfOJFQ1lWmeT69THrQrxyRumn0SU0gEHRYcnyFapDR7UKqvRd0ODfCBHvGM0DiCGIEGuWuSMtHHNPxhWbt6XfqWEZtw1hQMjpyUO92J/AHqYbiZJi0FsIzMpb2mr3PunqJd1cQjo0rl2S0CCDiLEKpN8biMY64JC0w/07FabGwpeWCHjAS5NyjFYi4uzcG7XQ3r7L9fYcMdcRbjlluwrkfVWs04Z1vGUSMnQH0bnBDKmNHZ8u5B4FICMhoLfcjtMTcaapPJMF+gSZVCFAc=",
        "questionId": "5471d31e68e34f48aa2de000abcd9a5a",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "7HugT2bLUMsIOYE9s1mmocpLFGDvAg+LkjUvwR1zVD8=",
                "optionId": "8bf3f856a16f47a4a7b209a7fc896801"
            },
            {
                "option": "yJ4QHOQzwVihN7MwLiBKb31GbBtMHoEM0FlPQTdFU6A=",
                "optionId": "c53c6c53639a4c97ad7c174c6f8b6834"
            },
            {
                "option": "Ha3UySt33jBedrvNn5AogF06WJSTWENb5/zIqLhVc5Q=",
                "optionId": "f0aa0a3d86d24259a43c86952579fb4f"
            },
            {
                "option": "IImGNiNSb3inQOK+cZGl2vbGv5mkuPbJQvQ0iPne1Zs=",
                "optionId": "dee8fb3dca1148d7b24fe1927402e306"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "f0aa0a3d86d24259a43c86952579fb4f",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "zq2GDok2VKi5ObIm43saHlraP3JM8htxZ4IGLhVgYRw1J5y+SSlKApgZPkZ09GXO80ebTAhNESw3B6NiIjySLehMUlvPceHAUT63jJ5z1wHuhTc2kw9Chz8Cr1s/l0aB07RDniCNx/iFpJ/4G3JvAA8M5W701wyab8x5if8e7T0=",
        "questionId": "6970d1030b2a42908c9c1993bf92d6b4",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "OLitqQSQqnpROPnz6lt48FV5V3n6dlG7um9hQX3gKr4=",
                "optionId": "f193cd4d3450431c9415245c3efe625e"
            },
            {
                "option": "+UZskvN8/db4dn27Kpnf8KJy8V6K7zwffuHT0Rml8n0=",
                "optionId": "be86ffdbd7af46fea31e5d31d66f4ff3"
            },
            {
                "option": "yRBzA7oxhLsZIpsW1Ejr5avCQa0uFcrkIUsGpohtHRo=",
                "optionId": "598cd2cc27a04064ae115be59e5113b3"
            },
            {
                "option": "+4xPvVbgRtjyZLG4dP/FvT2DtIHNrdMRNykeTftEKtg=",
                "optionId": "1cc63968671d4469885d20c50e533435"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "be86ffdbd7af46fea31e5d31d66f4ff3",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    },
    {
        "question": "POprwyEhmeawViGF9PP3Y53T0GmkIqTj2/6BWnIhSCvsrz9QAnSGnhTIvUyQ8arPQRCN8YoQSPE1VnOGsd3i2Q==",
        "questionId": "c5eed63125554c62b7a54a7767d3e1ec",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "Hw0OIutZKkyZ5DRGr2LxUlRuHtl5bUL3Da3ntAtRsh4=",
                "optionId": "b32b3e7669d24afca86796622d09c24d"
            },
            {
                "option": "Lum3WMsFyPBZHAsoSjlWZVgGotv8+HYRG8WBEbDdsyk=",
                "optionId": "fc4d1f45ef564da09c9cb357b95bea2e"
            },
            {
                "option": "LXXhrSS6EtPEeRdVqfERgvjzFPL1jGt3xo/KMFCCRyc=",
                "optionId": "1ef6e9b6c239436a8e8b923aab3938fb"
            },
            {
                "option": "HQUdhb8qTN3m0EITDLOClOQki77DJhr5ZmwnXQsu31o=",
                "optionId": "07245bb1afd642c0bf7a78754026cafd"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "1ef6e9b6c239436a8e8b923aab3938fb",
        "center": "IIT Kanpur"
    }
]